Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1930s-1992
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Joseph L. Fisher papers
1930s-1992
C0028
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
58.0 linear feet (116 boxes)
This collection relates to Fisher's career as an economist, educator, and U.S. Congressman. The materials include lectures and comments on conservation and natural resources, scrapbooks, pamphlets, appointment books, and correspondence. Materials that relate to his political career in U.S. House of Representatives include correspondence, speeches, press releases, reports, newsclippings, issue papers, testimony, statements, questionnaires, background publications, guidelines, charts, and legislation.
Fisher, Joseph L.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Margaret Fisher in 1992-1995.
Biographical Information
Joseph Lyman Fisher (1914-1992), economist, educator, author, and congressman, was born in Salesville, Rhode Island on January 11, 1914. After earning his undergraduate degree at Bowdoin College, Fisher went on to graduate work at the London School of Economics, Harvard University, and George Washington University. In 1942 he married the former Margaret Saunders Winslow. Fisher's career, spanning over fifty years, included planner for the National Resources Planning Board, economist for the United States Department of State, executive officer and economist for the Council of Economic Advisors, president of Resources for the Future, a member of the United States House of Representatives (1974-1981), Virginia Secretary of Human Resources, special assistant to the president of George Mason University, and president of the National Academy of Public Administration. In addition, Fisher was deeply involved in community activities, having been chairman of the Arlington County Board, chairman of the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA), president and chairman of the Washington Metropolitan Council of Governments (COG), and moderator and chairman of the board of the Unitarian Universalist Association. He also wrote several books, including World Prospects for Natural Resources (1964) and Resources in America's Future (1963).
Scope and Content
This collection is divided into three series.
Series 1 of the collection relates to Fisher's political career in the U.S. House of Representatives (1974-1981). The materials cover the years 1974-1992 and include correspondence, speeches, press releases, reports, newsclippings, issue papers, testimony, statements, questionnaires, background publications, guidelines, charts, and legislation.
Series 2 relates to Fisher's career as an economist, educator, and U.S. Congressman. The materials cover the years 1930s-1992 and include lectures and comments on conservation and natural resources, class notes, papers, and dissertation and thesis, scrapbooks, pamphlets, appointment books, and correspondence.
Series 3 consists of two flat boxes that contain awards, certificates, and diplomas for both Joseph and Margaret Fisher, as well as campaign posters, a large newspaper clipping, a large photograph, and scrapbook covers. Materials date from 1943 to 1992.
Arrangement
Organized into three series.
Series 1: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1992
Series 2: Academic Career/Government Appointments, 1930s-1992
Series 3: Oversize, 1943-1992
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the papers of other local and national politicians from Northern Virginia.
Index Terms
Persons:
Fisher, Joseph Lyman, 1914-1992.
Corporate Names:
George Mason University.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Ways and Means.
Geographical Names:
Arlington County (Va.)
Subjects:
Conservation of natural resources--Law and legislation--United States.; Energy policy--Law and legislation--United States.; Taxation--Law and legislation--United States.
Contents List
- Series 1: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1992
  Papers relate to Fisher's political career in U.S. House of Representatives (1974-1992). The materials cover the years 1974-1992 and include: correspondence, speeches, press releases, reports, newsclippings, issue papers, testimony, statements, questionnaires, background publications, guidelines, charts, and legislation.
  - 96th Congress, 2nd Session, John L. Norman - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 96th Congress, 2nd Session, Fisher Statements, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, co-signed letters, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, co-signed letters, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, news releases, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 96th Congress, 2nd Session, news releases, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, testimony, April - May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, amendments, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 96th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 2683, March 4, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Adding population-density factor to definition of Urban County; Banking, finance, urban affairs.
  - Nonresident income taxation H.R. 10116 and H.R. 11303, March 15, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 12, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Permit employees of House to contribute through payroll withholding; House administration.
  - 95th Congress, 2nd session, Fisher Bill H.R. 1536, February 6, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Established within the Department of State an Assistant Secretary for claims against foreign ministers and diplomats and awards just compensation for such claims.
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 936, April 21, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    To require a refund value for certain beverage containers; Interstate and foreign commerce.
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 3645, February 24, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Federal civilian and posted service employees rights; Post Office and civil service participation in political process.
  - 95th Congress, 2nd session, Fisher Bill H.R. 4620, January 24, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Special allowances to certain physicians employed by U.S.; Postal service and civil service.
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 955, January 4, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Grants for the construction of bikeways; Public work plus transportation.
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, general, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 95th Congress, 1st Session, general, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 95th Congress, 2nd Session, general, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 95th Congress, 2nd Session, general news releases, 1976; 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, H.R. 2449, January 15, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Prohibit increase in the price of food stamps; Agriculture.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 8552, July 15, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Gifts to National Arboretum; Agriculture.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 8778, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Human treatment of animals; Agriculture.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 56, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Disapproval of budget deferral of HUD planning program; Appropriates.
  - 1976 Fisher Bill, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Regarding Wilson Recomputation Bill; Armed Forces.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9142, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Recomputation of military retired pay; Armed Services.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 14341, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Prohibition of unions in the Armed Forces.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 4029, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Maintain commissary stores; Armed Services.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13005, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    National condominium and tenants rights act B,C and H.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 5028, February 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Termination of bank insurance.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13934, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    George Washington University charter; District of Columbia.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 15434 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Water rate structure; D.C. and public works committees.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 6360, April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Metro financing; District of Columbia.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10440, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Commission to study Federal payment to D.C.; District of Columbia.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 10798, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    D.C. medical and dental manpower; District of Columbia.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 15518, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Age discrimination in employment; Education and labor.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 8619 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Small business under OSHA; Education and labor.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13812, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Federal Procurement Policy Act; Government operations.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 744, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Impact of federal property on local government; Government operations.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 11108, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Interests on overdue contract payments; Government operations.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 14472, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Mihailovich movement; House administration.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 5543, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    American Folklife Center; House administration.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9103, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Public financing of Congressional campaigns; House administration.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 136, February - March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Withholding of state tax for House employees; House administration.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 294, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    John McCormack Sr. intern program; House administration.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 11875, March 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Potomac National River; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 12850, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    New River; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1228, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Brggs / Begich peaks in Alaska; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 5633, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Land use planning; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 6624, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Shenandoah wilderness; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 6892, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9222, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Manassas National Battlefield Park; Interior plus insular affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Diplomatic immunity bills with co-sponsors; International relations.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 14828, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Diplomatic immunity; International relations.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 15683 and H.R. 15684, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Diplomatic relations; International relations.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 351, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Sale of arms to Jordan; International relations.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 608, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Calling an Atlantic conference; International relations.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 9393, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Commission on regulatory reform; Interstate and foreign commerce.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R.12053, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Franchise practices; Interstate plus foreign commerce.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 15610, September 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Radio frequency interference; Interstate plus foreign commerce.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 15627, March 1, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Life support centers act; Interstate plus foreign commerce.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 3246, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Returnable beverage container act of 1975; Interstate plus foreign commerce.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 12178, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Relief of Edward J. Shea; Private Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1565, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Condemning murders of Letelier and Moffitt; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 2926, March 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Federal financial disclosure; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 3048, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Federal lobbying registration act; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9457, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Relief of Ruth Guilder; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10009, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Financial disclosure; Judiciary, official conduct.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10478, December 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Relief of Luisa Lavandez de Alvarez.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 254, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Robert E. Lee citizenship; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 432, March 18, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    D.C. Representation in Congress; Judiciary.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 7498, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Fish and wildlife service administration; Merchant Marine and fisheries.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10900, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Tinicum National Environmental Center; Merchant Marine plus fisheries.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13641, May 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Hatch Act revision; Post Office plus service.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13933, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Allowances for physicians; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 14061, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Increase civil service commission membership; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 1238, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Closing of Post Office; Civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 777, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Thomas Jefferson Day; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1063, August 27, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Nation volunteer firemen week; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 2660, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Civil service retirement for armed forces employees; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 2661, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Department of Defense employees under civil service; Post Office.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 3934, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Federal employees political activities act; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 5350, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Federal employees relocation; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 7604, May 30, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Regarding changes in federal employee health insurance; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9440, July 29, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Executive branch employees pay comparability; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9994, September 29, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Court leave for federal employees; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10060, October 7, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Disallow presidents plan for federal pay raise; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 10491, October 8, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Congressional pay freeze; Post Office plus civil service.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 5591, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Public works capital development; Public works.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 12784, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Government economy plus spending reform act; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1130, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Select committee on nuclear proliferation; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1317, June 16-17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Remove limitations on number of co-sponsors; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1345, June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Investigations by committee on official conduct; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 1436, July 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Ex-members prohibited from lobbying on House floor; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 466, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Open conference committee; Rules committee.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 496, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Select committee on MIA's; Rules committee.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 620, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Select committee on energy; Rules.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13215, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Unknown revolutionary war soldier; Veterans affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 4857, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Life insurance for vets with service; Connected disabilities, Veterans affairs.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13500, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Lobbying by public charities; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 13890, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Renters tax credit; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session Fisher Bill H.R. 15357, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Auto insurance for diplomats; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 1767, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Prohibit oil tariff for 90 days; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 3832, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Estate tax on farms; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 7131, May 20, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Condominium tax exemption; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 7694, June 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Nursing care under medicare; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 8021, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Lobbying by tax exempt organizations; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 8579, July 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Taxation of legal service fees; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9442, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Tax privacy act of 1975; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 9494, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Social security claims procedures; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 58, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Prohibit oil tariff until April 1, 1975; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, Fisher Bill H.R. 72, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Resolution disapproving ceiling on social security benefits; Ways and means.
  - 94th Congress, Fisher voting record, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 94th Congress, 1st and 2nd Session, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session, general, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 94th Congress, 2nd Session, general, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 94th Congress, 1st Session, general, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, March - December 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, May - August 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, September - December 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tax questionnaire, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous taxes, general, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, January - February 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous taxes, general, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous taxes, general, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, January - April 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ways and means committee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tax legislation, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Press releases, clippings, newsletters.
  - Taxes, miscellaneous correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous tax legislation, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous taxes, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Taxpayer sentiment, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Reform of Congress, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ted Taylor seminar; House reform seminar, January 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ted Taylor seminar; Congressional pay raise, January 31, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Select committee on committees, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Committee on committees, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ethics, issue paper no. 9 (Sundquist), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, July 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, April 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, May 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, May 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, January - April 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, May - December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means committee miscellaneous tax issues, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, January - February 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Administration tax packages, correspondence, March 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ways and means committee miscellaneous tax issues, correspondence, April - December 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Anti-inflamation material, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous taxes, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Copies of tax bill, correspondence, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means committee miscellaneous tax issues, correspondence, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee miscellaneous tax issues, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Taxes, miscellaneous issues, correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Administrative tax package, correspondence, August 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Administrative tax package, correspondence, September - October 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fisher amendment to revenue act of 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Revenue act of 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Tax administration, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ways and means committee tax policy as fiscal policy, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee Ford economic program, correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1980 tax cut bill (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1978 tax bill cut (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kemp-Roth tax cuts, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kemp-Roth tax cuts, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Kemp-Roth, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ways and means committee Ford tax cut proposal, October - December 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Value added tax, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Value added tax, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tax reform bill (background information), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Tax reform, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Tax reform (from miscellaneous file), 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Tax reform (from miscellaneous file), 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)